SEAN GRINDAL

COMSCI STUDENT & FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

HTTPS://SEANGRINDAL.DEV

PERSONAL PROFILE

Enthusiastic developer and student. Started working professionally as a contract frontend developer at the beginning of highschool. Experienced leading multiple development projects, and architecting internal development tools. I love to work closely with executives to bring about company visions and goals.

CONTACT

- hello@seangrindal.dev
- seangrindal.dev
- LinkedIn
- <u>Github</u>

LANGUAGES / SKILLS

- JS/ES6 (4/y)
- HTML/PUG (4/y)
- CSS/SCSS(4/y)
- Vue.js (3/y)
- Nuxt.js (2/y)
- Node.js (4/y)
- Wordpress (3/y)
- PHP (3/y)
- Python (1/y)
- Git (4/y)
- Notion (2/y)
- Organization and writing of company tech documentation
- Planning frontend web projects
- Architecting internal codebases and templates for code reusability

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Part-Time Consultant Developer

ANOA (Sept 2021 - Present)

- Responsible for planning and overseeing the development of ongoing client projects
- Continued onboarding of a new developer
- Maintenance of important codebases and documentation

Lead Developer

ANOA (Aug 2020 - Aug 2021)

- Led planning and development of various internal codebases, patterns, and templates used across client websites
- Architected a new headless CMS and frontend schema to be used across all client portfolio projects
- Responsible for an internal demos website to facilitate the design of client projects
- Vetted resumes and interviewed new potential developers
- Worked closely with the CEO on road mapping and company vision

Part-Time Contract Frontend Developer

Motiv (2018 - Present)

- Working closely with designers to program the frontend of various client websites using ES6, HTML, SCSS, Vue, Node.js
- Working with a team of other developers on larger web projects, to plan and develop web components
- Helped plan and develop internal frontend patterns

PROJECTS

Custom Cursor JS

- https://custom-cursor-js.netlify.app/

3D Equation Modeller

- https://seangrindal.dev/experiments/3d-equation-modeller/

View professional projects on my website

- https://seangrindal.dev

EDUCATION

University of Toronto

Computer Science '25

- 1st year, currently have a 4.0 GPA
- Discrete mathematics and proofs
- Analyzing running time and algorithm complexity